they showed it show again I didn’t
там показывали покажите еще раз не
see the chevronchik of
увидел шеврончик
this to someone and the card was shown
этого кому-то а карточку показывали
before that Yes yes I’m from Ukraine the
видно перед этим Да да я из Украины
city of Khmelnitsky wax cities of Russia
город Хмельницкий восковые города России
from the Moscow region of the Moscow region
с Московской области Московской области
why often people from the Moscow region
почему часто люди с Москвы области
say I’m from Moscow like they want there near
говорят Я из Москвы типа хотят там под
Moscow
Москвой
because  So I personally live just 80
потому что Вот я лично живу просто 80
kilometers from Moscow, and therefore it’s just, well,
километров от Москвы и поэтому просто ну
my city, let’s say you don’t know Moscow
город мой допустим вы не знаете Москву
for sure, you might
точно можете
not know
не знаю
No, I can see the city, that is, in the news
Нет я могу город то есть и в новостях
there and, in principle, on the Internet, I saw how you
там и в принципе в интернете видел как
support a special military operation
поддерживаете
Well, you know everything  very skeptical Well,
Ну знаете все очень скептически Ну
neutral Yes, neutral it’s
нейтрально Да нейтрально это как
like in my city, if you want news Yes,
в моем городе вот если ты хочешь новости
yesterday a Russian fueling rocket arrived,
Да вчера прилетела Российская ракета по
injured seven people, one of them,
заправке ранила семь человек одна из них
22 years old, a girl died, I heard heard I heard
22 года девушка погибло я слышал слышал
about it today,
мне уже сегодня об этом говорили здесь
22 years old, a girl died Yes, how can you  to
22 года девочка умерла Да как можно к
this neutral
этому нейтральным
Well, you know, I think that
Ну вот у меня знаете я вот считаю что
I have a friend, yes, he
вот у меня друг есть да вот он
comes from Donetsk
получается с Донецка
under  I can’t remember the name of a Donetsk village.
под Донецком село какое-то я название не
Here he had Grandfather’s grandmother and a
могу запомнить Вот у него бабушку Деда и
little sister, she killed him from your
сестренку маленькую убила с вашей
side, because of which she killed him
стороны прилетела из-за чего убила его
because Russia started the war
из-за того что Россия начала войну
correctly, but not at 14
правильно но не в 14
to 14, there was nobody there  didn’t kill
до 14 года никого там что-то не убивала
like that Donetsk Luhansk
так Донецке Луганске
classmate 14 had already arrived until the
одноклассница 14 уже приехал до
fourteenth year, didn’t kill anyone,
четырнадцатого года никого что-то не
so that’s it Dasha
так вот именно Даша всё началось Россия
started the war
Луганской области начало войну
then Ukraine fought in the
а против кого тогда воевала Украина в
Donetsk region,
Донецкой области
Donetsk wanted to withdraw, but against whom did it
Донецк хотел отойти но против кого она
fight,
воевала
as a matter of fact, against Donetsk against the
она как по сути против Донецка против
army of the Donetsk People's Republic
армии Донецкой народной Республики
was the Donetsk region and Donetsk
было Донецкая область и Донецк
what republic and where did it get
какая республика и откуда у него там
some kind of army from? They wanted to withdraw
какая-то армия Они хотели отойти
correctly, so let's Russian troops
правильно давайте так российских войск
there  it wasn’t like that, you want to say. Now
там не было так вы хотите сказать Теперь
you know the question of backfilling, how do you see
вопрос на засыпку знаете как смотрите
Ukraine is occupied by the Russian
Украина у нас оккупирован российской
army Kherson  and Ukraine, without a single
армии Херсон и Украина без единого
shot at Kherson, it turns out
выстрела по херсону получается
Ukraine knocked out 30,000 Russian
Украина выбила 30.000 российскую
personnel army from Kherson that they left and
кадровую армию из Херсона что они ушли и
went into Kherson calmly
зашла себе в Херсон спокойно Да
Yes, if Ukraine is so strong that it
так если Украина такая сильная что
was able to Russian army 30 thousand people
смогла российскую армию 30 тысяч человек
with aviation with this with satellite
с авиацией с этом со спутниковой
reconnaissance with
разведкой с
helicopters with artillery so  knock out of
вертолетами с артиллерией так выбить из
Kherson so calmly, why is the
Херсона так спокойно то почему та же
same Ukraine just some
самая Украина каких-то просто Шахтеров
unarmed miners Yes, it couldn’t knock 8 years out of
безоружных Да не могла выбить 8 лет из
Donetsk, you can tell me for some reason
Донецка можете мне сказать почему-то
Well, you know, I
Ну знаете
have information that let’s say that
у меня вот есть информация что допустим
now you have to surrender in the army not only
сдаваться сейчас у вас в армии не только
Ukrainian they  were in the year 14 if you
украинские они были в 14 году если так
look like this, these mercenaries were all 8 years old,
смотреть эти наемники были все 8 лет
though it’s not now where to take you mean
правда не сейчас где-то взять Вы имеете
mercenaries, that is, from our side
ввиду наемники то есть с нашей стороны
Here are ours what will come out if these
Вот наши что у нас выйдет вот если эти
mercenaries used to be so how many of
наемниками и раньше были так сколько там
these mercenaries are there a million 2 million  10
этих наемников миллион 2 миллиона 10
people how many well the number I can’t
человек сколько ну число я не могу
say I had such information
сказать у меня такой информации
Why did the Ukrainian army with the same
были Почему украинская армия с этими же
mercenaries and for 8 years not be able to  la
наемниками да за 8 лет не смогла
calmly take away Donetsk so from some
спокойно отобрать Донецк так от каких-то
miners slept with sticks And here the
Шахтёров спал с палками А тут у
Russian army with aviation
российской армии с авиацией